/* 3 SAMPLE DECKS OF CARDS for the demo route */


module.exports = [





	/* DECK #1 KOREAN */
	[
		{question : 'School', answer : '학교'}, 
		{question : 'Pencil', answer : '연필'}, 
		{question : 'Table', answer : '탁자'}, 
		{question : 'Box', answer : '상자'}, 
		{question : 'Skin', answer : '피부'},

		{question : 'Classroom', answer : '교실'}, 
		{question : 'Textbook', answer : '교과서'}, 
		{question : 'War', answer : '전쟁'}, 
		{question : 'Gift', answer : '선물'}, 
		{question : 'Price', answer : '가격'},

		{question : 'Paper', answer : '종이'}, 
		{question : 'Presentation', answer : '발표'}, 
		{question : 'Score', answer : '점수'}, 
		{question : 'Success', answer : '성공'}, 
		{question : 'Reply', answer : '대답'},

		{question : 'Glass', answer : '유리'}, 
		{question : 'Delivery', answer : '배달'}, 
		{question : 'Newspaper', answer : '신문'}, 
		{question : 'Eyeglasses', answer : '안경'}, 
		{question : 'Protein', answer : '단백질'},

		{question : 'Line', answer : '선'}, 
		{question : 'Message', answer : '문자'}, 
		{question : 'Device', answer : '장치'}, 
		{question : 'Screen', answer : '화면'}, 
		{question : 'Dot', answer : '점'},

		{question : 'Doctor', answer : '의사'}, 
		{question : 'Expert', answer : '전문가'}, 
		{question : 'Tool', answer : '도구'}, 
		{question : 'Garden', answer : '정원'}, 
		{question : 'Food', answer : '음식'},

		{question : 'Rice', answer : '쌀'}, 
		{question : 'Bread', answer : '빵'}, 
		{question : 'Error', answer : '오류'}, 
		{question : 'Chemistry', answer : '화학'}, 
		{question : 'Region', answer : '지역'},

		{question : 'Song', answer : '노래'}, 
		{question : 'Vehicle', answer : '차량'}, 
		{question : 'Blood', answer : '혈액'}, 
		{question : 'Swimming Pool', answer : '수영장'}, 
		{question : 'Material', answer : '물질'},

		{question : 'Obstacle', answer : '장애물'}, 
		{question : 'Odor', answer : '냄새'}, 
		{question : 'Peach', answer : '복숭아'}, 
		{question : 'Bird', answer : '새'}, 
		{question : 'Water', answer : '물'},

		{question : 'Mystery', answer : '미지수'}, 
		{question : 'Secret', answer : '비밀'}, 
		{question : 'Rumor', answer : '소문'}, 
		{question : 'Elbow', answer : '팔꿈치'}, 
		{question : 'Quote', answer : '인용구'},

		{question : 'Compliment', answer : '칭찬'}, 
		{question : 'Criticism', answer : '비판'}, 
		{question : 'Arrow', answer : '화살'}, 
		{question : 'Language', answer : '언어'}, 
		{question : 'Path', answer : '경로'},

		{question : 'Flour', answer : '밀가루'}, 
		{question : 'Noodles', answer : '국수'}, 
		{question : 'Office', answer : '사무실'}, 
		{question : 'Cabinet', answer : '보관장'}, 
		{question : 'Carpet', answer : '카펫'},

		{question : 'Soil', answer : '흙'}, 
		{question : 'Flower', answer : '꽃'}, 
		{question : 'Color', answer : '색깔'}, 
		{question : 'Trash', answer : '쓰레기'}, 
		{question : 'Function', answer : '기능'},

		{question : 'House', answer : '집'}, 
		{question : 'Asset', answer : '자산'}, 
		{question : 'Possession', answer : '소유'}, 
		{question : 'Goal', answer : '목표'}, 
		{question : 'Life', answer : '인생'},

		{question : 'Moment', answer : '순간'}, 
		{question : 'God', answer : '신'}, 
		{question : 'Lightning', answer : '번개'}, 
		{question : 'Vinyl', answer : '비닐'}, 
		{question : 'Expense', answer : '비용'},

		{question : 'Peace', answer : '푱화'}, 
		{question : 'Corruption', answer : '타락'}, 
		{question : 'Official', answer : '공식'}, 
		{question : 'Opinion', answer : '의견'}, 
		{question : 'Candle', answer : '양초'}
	],





	/* DECK #2 SPANISH */
	[
		{question : 'School', answer : 'escuela'}, 
		{question : 'Pencil', answer : 'lápiz'}, 
		{question : 'Table', answer : 'mesa'}, 
		{question : 'Box', answer : 'caja'}, 
		{question : 'Skin', answer : 'piel'},

		{question : 'Classroom', answer : 'aula'}, 
		{question : 'Textbook', answer : 'libro de texto'}, 
		{question : 'War', answer : 'guerra'}, 
		{question : 'Gift', answer : 'regalo'}, 
		{question : 'Price', answer : 'paz'},

		{question : 'Paper', answer : 'papel'}, 
		{question : 'Presentation', answer : 'presentación'}, 
		{question : 'Score', answer : 'puntuación'}, 
		{question : 'Success', answer : 'éxito'}, 
		{question : 'Reply', answer : 'respuesta'},

		{question : 'Glass', answer : 'vidrio'}, 
		{question : 'Delivery', answer : 'entrega'}, 
		{question : 'Newspaper', answer : 'periódico'}, 
		{question : 'Eyeglasses', answer : 'anteojos'}, 
		{question : 'Protein', answer : 'proteína'},

		{question : 'Line', answer : 'línea'}, 
		{question : 'Message', answer : 'mensaje'}, 
		{question : 'Device', answer : 'dispositivo'}, 
		{question : 'Screen', answer : 'pantalla'}, 
		{question : 'Dot', answer : 'punto'},

		{question : 'Doctor', answer : 'doctor'}, 
		{question : 'Expert', answer : 'experto'}, 
		{question : 'Tool', answer : 'herramienta'}, 
		{question : 'Garden', answer : 'jardín'}, 
		{question : 'Food', answer : 'comida'},

		{question : 'Rice', answer : 'arroz'}, 
		{question : 'Bread', answer : 'pan'}, 
		{question : 'Error', answer : 'error'}, 
		{question : 'Chemistry', answer : 'química'}, 
		{question : 'Region', answer : 'región'},

		{question : 'Song', answer : 'canción'}, 
		{question : 'Vehicle', answer : 'vehículo'}, 
		{question : 'Blood', answer : 'sangre'}, 
		{question : 'Swimming Pool', answer : 'piscina'}, 
		{question : 'Material', answer : 'material'},

		{question : 'Obstacle', answer : 'obstáculo'}, 
		{question : 'Odor', answer : 'olor'}, 
		{question : 'Peach', answer : 'melocotón'}, 
		{question : 'Bird', answer : 'pájaro'}, 
		{question : 'Water', answer : 'agua'},

		{question : 'Mystery', answer : 'misterio'}, 
		{question : 'Secret', answer : 'secreto'}, 
		{question : 'Rumor', answer : 'rumor'}, 
		{question : 'Elbow', answer : 'codo'}, 
		{question : 'Quote', answer : 'cita'},

		{question : 'Compliment', answer : 'cumplido'}, 
		{question : 'Criticism', answer : 'crítica'}, 
		{question : 'Arrow', answer : 'flecha'}, 
		{question : 'Language', answer : 'idioma'}, 
		{question : 'Path', answer : 'camino'},

		{question : 'Flour', answer : 'harina'}, 
		{question : 'Noodles', answer : 'fideos'}, 
		{question : 'Office', answer : 'oficina'}, 
		{question : 'Cabinet', answer : 'gabinete'}, 
		{question : 'Carpet', answer : 'alfombra'},

		{question : 'Soil', answer : 'suelo'}, 
		{question : 'Flower', answer : 'flor'}, 
		{question : 'Color', answer : 'color'}, 
		{question : 'Trash', answer : 'basura'}, 
		{question : 'Function', answer : 'función'},

		{question : 'House', answer : 'casa'}, 
		{question : 'Asset', answer : 'activo'}, 
		{question : 'Possession', answer : 'posesión'}, 
		{question : 'Goal', answer : 'objetivo'}, 
		{question : 'Life', answer : 'vida'},

		{question : 'Moment', answer : 'momento'}, 
		{question : 'God', answer : 'dios'}, 
		{question : 'Lightning', answer : 'relámpago'}, 
		{question : 'Vinyl', answer : 'vinilo'}, 
		{question : 'Expense', answer : 'gasto'},

		{question : 'Peace', answer : 'paz'}, 
		{question : 'Corruption', answer : 'corrupción'}, 
		{question : 'Official', answer : 'oficial'}, 
		{question : 'Opinion', answer : 'opinión'}, 
		{question : 'Candle', answer : 'vela'}
	],





	/* DECK #3 JAPANESE */
	[
		{question : 'School', answer : '学校'}, 
		{question : 'Pencil', answer : '鉛筆'}, 
		{question : 'Table', answer : '表'}, 
		{question : 'Box', answer : 'ボックス'}, 
		{question : 'Skin', answer : '肌'},

		{question : 'Classroom', answer : '教室'}, 
		{question : 'Textbook', answer : '教科書'}, 
		{question : 'War', answer : '戦争'}, 
		{question : 'Gift', answer : '贈り物'}, 
		{question : 'Price', answer : '価格'},

		{question : 'Paper', answer : '論文'}, 
		{question : 'Presentation', answer : 'プレゼンテーション'}, 
		{question : 'Score', answer : 'スコア'}, 
		{question : 'Success', answer : '成功'}, 
		{question : 'Reply', answer : '返信'},

		{question : 'Glass', answer : 'ガラス'}, 
		{question : 'Delivery', answer : '配達'}, 
		{question : 'Eyeglasses', answer : '眼鏡'}, 
		{question : 'Newspaper', answer : '新聞'}, 
		{question : 'Protein', answer : 'タンパク質'},

		{question : 'Line', answer : 'ライン'}, 
		{question : 'Message', answer : 'メッセージ'}, 
		{question : 'Device', answer : 'デバイス'}, 
		{question : 'Screen', answer : 'スクリーン'}, 
		{question : 'Dot', answer : 'ドット'},

		{question : 'Doctor', answer : '医者'}, 
		{question : 'Expert', answer : '専門家'}, 
		{question : 'Tool', answer : 'ツール'}, 
		{question : 'Garden', answer : '庭'}, 
		{question : 'Food', answer : '食べ物'},

		{question : 'Rice', answer : '米'}, 
		{question : 'Bread', answer : 'パン'}, 
		{question : 'Error', answer : 'エラー'}, 
		{question : 'Chemistry', answer : '化学'}, 
		{question : 'Region', answer : '地域'},

		{question : 'Song', answer : '歌'}, 
		{question : 'Vehicle', answer : '乗り物'}, 
		{question : 'Blood', answer : '血液'}, 
		{question : 'Swimming Pool', answer : 'プール'}, 
		{question : 'Material', answer : '素材'},

		{question : 'Obstacle', answer : '障害物'}, 
		{question : 'Odor', answer : '匂い'}, 
		{question : 'Peach', answer : '桃'}, 
		{question : 'Bird', answer : '鳥'}, 
		{question : 'Water', answer : '水'},

		{question : 'Mystery', answer : '謎'}, 
		{question : 'Secret', answer : '秘密'}, 
		{question : 'Rumor', answer : '噂'}, 
		{question : 'Elbow', answer : '肘'}, 
		{question : 'Quote', answer : '見積もり'},

		{question : 'Compliment', answer : '褒め言葉'}, 
		{question : 'Criticism', answer : '批判'}, 
		{question : 'Arrow', answer : '矢'}, 
		{question : 'Language', answer : '言語'}, 
		{question : 'Path', answer : '道'},

		{question : 'Flour', answer : '小麦粉'}, 
		{question : 'Noodles', answer : '麺類'}, 
		{question : 'Office', answer : 'オフィス'}, 
		{question : 'Cabinet', answer : 'キャビネット'}, 
		{question : 'Carpet', answer : 'カーペット'},

		{question : 'Soil', answer : '土壌'}, 
		{question : 'Flower', answer : '花'}, 
		{question : 'Color', answer : '色'}, 
		{question : 'Trash', answer : 'ごみ'}, 
		{question : 'Function', answer : '機能'},

		{question : 'House', answer : '家'}, 
		{question : 'Asset', answer : '資産'}, 
		{question : 'Possession', answer : '所持'}, 
		{question : 'Goal', answer : '目標'}, 
		{question : 'Life', answer : '人生'},

		{question : 'Moment', answer : '瞬間'}, 
		{question : 'God', answer : '神'}, 
		{question : 'Lightning', answer : '稲妻'}, 
		{question : 'Vinyl', answer : 'ビニール'}, 
		{question : 'Expense', answer : '経費'},

		{question : 'Peace', answer : '平和'}, 
		{question : 'Corruption', answer : '腐敗'}, 
		{question : 'Official', answer : '公式'}, 
		{question : 'Opinion', answer : '意見'}, 
		{question : 'Candle', answer : 'ろうそく'}
	]


];